williamhill.com 2008-11-13

# Privacy Policy

**Policy Statement**

The following describes the information gathering and dissemination practices for the websites operated by William Hill Credit Limited (ICO registration number Z6700548) and other subsidiaries of William Hill Plc (together 'William Hill'), including without limitation **[www.willhill.com](http://www.willhill.com/)** , **www.williamhill.co.uk** , **[www.williamhillcasino.com](http://www.williamhillcasino.com/), ****[www.williamhillskillgames.com](http://www.williamhillskillgames.com/)** and **[www.williamhillpoker.com](http://www.williamhillpoker.com/) (the "Websites")**. Your personal data (meaning any information about You which is personally identifiable, such as your name, address, telephone number or email address and which is generally referred to throughout this document as "Your information") will be processed by William Hill Credit Limited and by other companies in the William Hill Group. Please note that this site contains links to other sites and that William Hill is not responsible for the privacy practices or content of such sites. ****

By using the Websites you acknowledge that you have read the terms of this Privacy Policy and that you consent to the use of Your information for the purposes set out in this Privacy Policy.

If you do not wish to provide Your information on the basis set out in this Privacy Policy you should not complete the personal details in the spaces provided. However, in that case, we regret that you will not be able to make full use of the Websites. We also offer visitors an "opt-out" option at any time they wish to cease receiving e-mails or other information from us.

As technology continues to develop, this Privacy Policy may need changing in order to provide the best possible service to our site visitors. We would recommend you to check and make sure that you have read our most recent policy statement when you visit one of our Websites.

**What type of information we collect and how it is used**

William Hill collects Your information during the account registration process and you may choose to submit Your Information to obtain information or submit a comment, or to be kept informed of special offers and promotions. 

William Hill will only use Your Information, including sharing Your Information with third party data processors, for:

  * setting up, operating and managing your account;
  * providing the services requested of us (including those requested as part of the account opening process);
  * verifying the accuracy of Your Information, including disclosure of such information to third parties (including financial institutions, age verification and credit reporting agencies) in connection with such purposes (a record of the search will be retained and the third party may use the information to assist other companies for verification purposes); 
  * preparing demographic statistics and to display appropriate individualized advertisements and content; 
  * periodically sending members written communications to announce important service changes, technical issue updates and changes to terms and conditions and/or rules;
  * complying with our regulatory duties, obligations and responsibilities under the UK Gambling Act and to the Gambling Commission in the UK and the relevant regulators in the other jurisdictions where it carries out a regulated activity; and
  * conforming to legal requirements or complying with legal processes or acting to protect the interests of sporting bodies or other qualified bodies. 

William Hill will not send you unsolicited information regarding any third party commercial offers or advertisements.

William Hill may use your username and/or first name and region for advertising or promotional purposes. 

Telephone calls to and from our Customer Services Department are recorded for training and security purposes.

We may transfer Your information in the event of business sale or insolvency.

If at any time you wish us to stop processing Your Information for the above purposes, then you will be required to contact us.

**Cookies**

William Hill uses **cookies** to obtain non-personal information from on-line visitors to provide them with the best possible personalised on-line experience. Cookies are small markers sent by our web server to your web browser and they enable us to improve the Websites and better tailor them to meet your needs. We use cookies to analyse site usage, improve our content and product offerings and to customise promotional efforts, site content and layout. You can find out more about how Internet sites use cookies on [www.aboutcookies.org](http://www.aboutcookies.org/). 

If you wish to turn off cookies, please consult the "Help" menu on the menu bar of most browsers, which will tell you how to prevent your browser from accepting new cookies, how to have the browser notify you when you receive new cookies and how to prevent cookies altogether. If you do disable cookies, we may be unable to optimise your visit to our site and/or you may not be eligible for certain offers / promotions. 

**Overseas transfer of Your information**

In connection with the provision of its services, William Hill may need to transfer data (including personal information) to other William Hill group companies that are not incorporated in the UK, including William Hill Gibraltar Limited and William Hill Malta Limited. ****

Emails and other contacts between you and our Customer Services Department are logged and processed through RightNow Technologies Inc's contact management solution, which is based in the United States of America and a signatory to the US ‘safe harbour’ scheme. RightNow provide a secure hosted environment for all contact data. The data is not accessible to or shared with any parties external to William Hill. RightNow can be found at [www.rightnow.com](http://www.rightnow.com/).

**Updating Your information**

You may update or delete Your information at any time from within your William Hill account by clicking the My Account/Change Details button on the navigation bar once logged in.

You may obtain a copy of Your information held by William Hill by contacting us at [customerservices@williamhill.co.uk](mailto:customerservices@williamhill.co.uk) and requesting a copy. We do require up to forty (40) days' notice to enable us to comply with such a request.

**Contacting us**

If at any time you believe that William Hill has not adhered to the principles contained within this Privacy Policy, please notify us by email at [customerservices@williamhill.co.uk](mailto:customerservices@williamhill.co.uk) and we will use all commercially reasonable efforts to promptly determine and correct the problem.

Questions regarding this statement should be directed to [customerservices@williamhill.co.uk](mailto:customerservices@williamhill.co.uk) or by post to:

Customer Services Manager  
William Hill PLC  
7th Floor  
Milton House  
Charter Row  
Sheffield  
S1 3FZ  

**This Privacy Policy was last updated on 8th July 2008**
